<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Random Flea</title>
    <link>https://randomflea.dev/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Random Flea</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>High Tech Amish</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:37:58 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://randomflea.dev/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA Security&#43; Certification</title>
      <link>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tech/sec&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 16:37:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tech/sec&#43;/</guid>
      <description>I successfully passed my Security+ certification exam in April. I started studying August 2022, but having a baby and starting a business made studying take a bit longer than usual. Once things kind of started settling down, I was able to dedicate more hours per day to study and felt I was ready after a couple weeks.
I went through the CompTIA training with the complete bundle. I recieved access to CertMaster Practice, CertMaster Learn + Labs, and 2 exam vouchers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Hugo Site with Cactus theme and Isso Comments</title>
      <link>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tutorials/hugo-cactus-isso-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 12:21:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tutorials/hugo-cactus-isso-setup/</guid>
      <description>I had been using flask to run my personal site, then decided to switch to Hugo for simplicity. I looked through the Hugo Themes and really liked the Cactus Theme. It&amp;rsquo;s minimal and just looks better in my opinion. It had places for my blog, projects, and info about me which is all I needed for now. I wanted to add a comment section to my blog posts. Disqus is the big one but I don&amp;rsquo;t like the tracking they do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Setup of a Rocky Linux VPS</title>
      <link>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tutorials/rocky-linux-vps-initial-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 12:21:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tutorials/rocky-linux-vps-initial-setup/</guid>
      <description>Initial Setup of a Rocky Linux VPS So you just got a VPS with Rocky Linux installed on it (this guide will work for CentOS, RHEL, and Alma Linux too) and you have questions about it. How do you keep this secure on the Internet? How do you connect to it? Here are a few simple steps to keep your VPS secure.
Prerequisites Rocky Linux Installed (or CentOS, RHEL, or Alma Linux) Root access to server Terminal access (we&amp;rsquo;ll be connecting with SSH) Initial Connection Most VPS providers have SSH access setup by default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Over the Wire Bandit 1 4</title>
      <link>https://randomflea.dev/posts/wargames/over-the-wire-bandit-1-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 16:38:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://randomflea.dev/posts/wargames/over-the-wire-bandit-1-4/</guid>
      <description>Over The Wire Intro I&amp;rsquo;m starting a series on Over the Wire Wargames. Each wargame has different levels you progress through to beat it. It provides a fun way to learn security concepts from the very basics to the advanced. It gives you roadmap to take you through each wargame so that they build on what you learned from the others. All you have to do is ssh into the room and start figuring out how to get the password for the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zero to Mastery Academy Review</title>
      <link>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tech/zero-to-mastery-academy-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 16:37:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tech/zero-to-mastery-academy-review/</guid>
      <description>While I was looking for a way to learn web development, I found many resources to try. I wanted to go the free route first so I tried The Odin Project first. I liked the structure of it and the cool projects, felt like I learned better with videos instead of text. The Odin Project is a great resource and I may go back to revisit it, but I needed a different format to learn faster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My It Journey</title>
      <link>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tech/my-it-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 12:21:45 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://randomflea.dev/posts/tech/my-it-journey/</guid>
      <description>I always had a fascination with computers and wondering how they worked. This led to me taking a computer and networking course at a local tech school during my junior and senior years of high school. I had free range to work on whatever interested me. Which at that time was coding and security. Those remain the areas I enjoy the most. After graduating high school I went on to a community college to get my general education classes out of the way and use a scholarship I had earned.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
